Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.twelve Mss.B.B61.inventory12
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents S
  - Schitzsch
    - To Boas, 1907 July 23
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 July 17
  - Schlagenhaufen, Otto (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 25
  - Schlauch, Margaret (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 28
    - See FB open letter, Spain, Replies, 1938 Jan.
  - Schlee, A. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1923 May 7
  - Schleinitz, Emil von (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 20
  - Schleiter, F. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 29
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 27; 2p
  - Schlesinger, George (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 30
    - To Frank, Karl Geo., 1920 June 3
  - Schlesinger, K. (Box 79)
    - To Szilard, 1933 May 2; 3p
      - (enc. with Leibowitz to Boas, E.P.), 1933 May 4
    - From Szilard, 1933 May 9
      (also to Marschak)
  - Schlesische Gesellschaft für vaterlandische Cultur (Box 79)
    see Wolf, B.
  - Schlesischer altertums Verein (Box 79)
    - 1936 June 30
  - Schlesischer Bankverein (Box 79)
    - 1927 Jan. 7
  - Schlick, M. (Box 79)
    - To Dewey, John, 1936 Jan. 25; 2p
      - (enc. with Dewey, J., 1936 Nov. 30
  - Schlossberg, Ruth (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 2; 4p
  - Schmann, W. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 19
  - Schmeding, O. (Box 79)
    - also Walter, M., 1931 Nov. 14; 2p
  - Schmeide, Louis B. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1891
  - Schmeltz, J.D.E. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1889 June 19
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1889 June 18
    - To Boas, 1890 Mar. 14
    - JDES -- to M. Boas Jr., 1891 Jan. 9
  - Schmetterling, Max (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 22
  - Schmid, Reichard (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1929 Sep. 12
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1929 Sep. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 2; 2p
  - Schmid, Willi (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 15
  - Schmidt, Carl T. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1939 Aug. 7
  - Schmidt, Emil (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1894 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1886 Mar. 12
  - Schmidt, Enoch (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1924 July 29; 2p
  - Schmidt, Erich F. (Box 79)
    Native American Images note
    Folders #3, 4, 5, 6: Pottery
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 21
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1928 Sep. 5
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 3
    - From Boas, 1935 Sep. 24
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1925 May 30; 5p
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 15; 5p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 17; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 18, 1927 June 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 23; 11p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 14; 11p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 28; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sep. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 25; 3p
      - Hittite Report 1, 1929 June 28; 18p
      - Hittite Report 2, 1929 July 12; 8p
      - Hittite Report 3, 1929 July 26; 11p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 16; 2p
      - Hittite Report 4, 1929 Aug. 16; 13p
      - Hittite Report 5, 1929 Aug. 30; 13p
      - Hittite Report 6, 1929 Sep. 15; 11p
      - Hittite Report 7, 1929 Sep. 31; 16p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 12; 2p
      - Hittite Report 8, 1929 Oct. 21; 7p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 29
    - To Boas, 1930 July 20; 6p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 4
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1935 July 16
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 5
  - Schmidt, [Geheimrat] F., Konigliche Kunst Mus., Berlin (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1908 Sep. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 11; 5p
    - From Boas, 1909 June 14; 3p
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1910 June 25
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1907 June 28
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 6; 3p
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 7; 4p
  - Schmidt, [Geheimrat] P.W. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 11; 4p
    - From Boas, 1907 July 31
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 11; 4p
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1907 July 5
    - To Boas, 1912 June 12
    - To Boas, 1913 July 25
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 26; 7p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 3; 2p
  - Schmidt, George P. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 28
  - Schmidt, Gustav [Gusti] (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 14
  - Schmidt, M. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 21
  - Schmidt, Max - Mus. für Volkerkunde, Berlin (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1907 July 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 July 18
  - Schmidt, N. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 13
      - see Tyler, J.M. from FB, 1919 Nov. 13
  - Schmidt, R.C. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 1; 3p
  - Schmidt?, R.W. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 15; 2p
  - Schmidt, [Father] W. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 21
  - Schmidt, [Dr.] W. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 10; 2p
  - Schmidt, William M. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1941 July 31
    - To Boas, 1941 July 12
  - Schmidt-Ott, [Staatsminister Dr.] F. Notgemeinshaft der deutschen Wissensh. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 4, 17, 24, 27, 29
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 13, 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1923 Sep. 21; 2p
    - enc. Steinen, Karl v., 1926 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1930 June 4
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 27
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1931 June 1
    - From Boas, 1931 July 3
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 19
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 1
    - From Boas, 1933 June 26
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 8; 3pand
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1928 July 9
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 3
      - see FB to Thoma, W.K., 1930 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1931 June 30
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1933 May 2; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 8
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 28
    - From Heuser, F.W.J., 1931 Dec. 8
    - From Klenze, C. v. enc. Busse, Gisela V., 1931 Aug. 2
    - To Thun, Ferdinand, 1931 Oct. 3; 6p
  - Schmitt, F. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1935 June 6; 3p
  - Schnap-Schroder, Gerhard (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 28
  - Schneider, [Prof. Pharmacology]? (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1921 May 6
  - Schneider, Albert (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 12; 2p
  - Schneider, Doris (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1936 June 22
  - Schneider, Frederick F. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 2
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 25
  - Schneider, H.W. (Box 79)
    - From HWS, 1934 Jan. 23
  - Schneider, I. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 15
  - Schneider, Kurt (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 23
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1928 May 23
    - From Boas, 1928 July 5
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 1
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 15; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 6; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 5; 2p
      - enc. copy letter Erdman, H.E. to Palmer, A.M., 1927 Nov. 9; 2pand
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 29; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 9; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 26; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 10; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 30; 5p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 16; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sep. 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 24; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 10; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 16; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 9; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 13
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1930 June 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 29; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 10; 2p
    - KS -- to Lohmann, 1933 June 28
    - KS -- to Lohmann, 1933 June 21; 2p
    - KS -- to Lohmann, 1933 Aug. 30; 2p
    - enc. Lehmann to v. Hofe dated, 1933 Sep. 6
    - KS -- to Lohmann, 1933 Aug. 30
    - enc. Lehmann, W. to KS, 1933 Aug. 25
    - enc. v. Hofe to KS, 1933 Sep. 1
    - KS -- to Lohmann, 1933 Oct. 28
    - KS -- to Lohmann, 1933 Dec. 20; 2p
    - KS -- to Lohmann, 1934 May 7
    - KS -- to Lohmann, 1934 June 23
    - KS -- to Lohmann, 1934 Sep. 18
    - KS -- to Lohmann, 1934 Nov. 6; 3p
    - To Jarres, 1933 June 7
      - enc. Pflüger, A., 1933 June 7
  - Schneider, Louis R. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1891 Oct. 30
  - Schneiderman, Harry (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1934 June 26
    - From Boas, 1934 July 20
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 13
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 28
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 9
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1940 May 27
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1933 May 2
    - To Boas, 1933 May 12
    - To Boas, 1933 June 19
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 6
    - (encs. Zollschan, T. to Warburg, F.M. and Warburg, M. 1933 Dec. 30), 1934 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 15
    - (enc. FB's Aryans and Non-Aryans), 1934 Mar. 5
    - (enc. Zollschan, J. "Die Bedeutung des Rassenfaktors...), 1934 Apr. 24
    - (enc. re Masaryk from Die Wahrheit May 18), 1934 June 25
    - To Boas, 1934 June 25
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1935 July 9
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1936 July 2
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1939 May 4
    - To Boas, 1939 July 5
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 12
  - Schnütgen (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 4
  - Schobinger, J.J. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 5
  - Schoch, M. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 4; 2p
  - Schoene? [General Direktor, Kgl. Mus.] (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1885 May 16
  - Schoenemann, F. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 June 14
    - To Boas, 1920 June 23
  - Schoenfeld, Dudley (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 17
  - Schoepperle, G. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1918 July 31
    - To Boas, 1918 July 23
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 4; ap
  - Schofer, Richard H.A. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 17
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 13
    - To Boas, 1920 July 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 15
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 7; 2p
  - Scholefield, E.P. (Box 79)
    - To Teit, J.A., 1907 Apr. 24
      (on margin: FB to Hurlburt, I.)
  - Scholz, Arnulf (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 15; 2p
      (enc. his Archiv für Polarforschung)
  - Scholz, Richard F. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 19
  - Schonberg, Mary G. (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 15
  - School of American Archaeology (Box 79)
    - Minutes by Mitchell Carroll, 1908 July 13
    - Minutes, by annual meeting, Toronto, 1908 Dec. 28; 3p
  - School and Society (Box 79)
    - see FB open letter, 1913 Dec. 31
  - Schrabisch, Max (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1905 June 12
    - To Boas, 1905 June 10
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 8
  - Schreiber, R. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1908 Sep. 11
  - Schreiber, Witold (Box 79)
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 21
    - To Boas re phys. development Jewish population., undated; 2p
    - (re rendezvous time.), undated
    - (Anthropometrical study in Arch. Anthrop., v. 34, pp. 256-269), 1907
    - To Boas re phys. development Jewish population., 1908 Aug. 11
    - To Boas re phys. development Jewish population., 1908 Aug. 18
    - To Boas re phys. development Jewish population., 1908 Sep. 11
    - To Boas re phys. development Jewish population., 1909 Mar. 8
  - Schreiner, K.E. (Box 79)
    - To Nansen, F., 1926 Apr. 12; 3p
    - To Nansen, F., 1926 Apr. 12; copy
  - Schreitleitung "Der Angriff" (Box 79)
    - From Oetteking, B., 1932 June 3
  - Schriefer, L. (Box 79)
    - To Boas, 1926 May 4
  - Schrijnen, J. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1930 May 19
    - From Boas, 1930 June 2
    - From Boas, 1930 June 12
    - From Boas, 1930 July 11
    - From Boas, 1930 July 16
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1932 May 2
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 19
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb.
      - (encs. Bally, C. to JS June 23/28; Karlgren, B. to JS Feb. 10/28; and Folkierski, W. to Société des nations Oct. 13/28), 1928 Oct. 25; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 10
      - (enc. Comite... linguistes), 1929 June 30
      - Ordre du jour, 1929 June 14-15)
    - To Boas, 1929 July 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 13
    - To Boas, 1929 July 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Sep. 7
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 31; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 5
    - To Boas, 1930 May 20
    - To Boas, 1930 May 30
    - To Boas, 1930 June 26
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 9
    - To Boas, 1931 July 6
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1932 May 16
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1932 June 21
      - (list enclosed), 1932 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1937 May 10
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 20
    - From Bally, C., 1928 June 23
    - From Karlgren, B., 1928 Feb. 10
    - From Mercier, Ch., 1929 June 27
    - To Mercier, Ch., 1929 July 4; 2p
    - To Sechehaye, A., 1930 Feb. 18
    - To Luchaire, J., 1928 Dec. 14; 2p
      - (orignally with JL to Insti.... intellecuale, 1928 Dec. 3)
  - Schristain?? (Box 80)
    - Naturhistorisches Hofmuseum, 1920 Nov. 26; 3p
  - Schroeder, H. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1930 May 5
    - From Boas, 1930 July 15
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 20
  - Schroetter, Dr. Erich v. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 9
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 1
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1938 June 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 1
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1938 June 7
      - also editorial signed Martin Hall, 1938 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 11
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 8
    - To Bohn, Frank, 1940 Jan. 29
    - From Lips, J.E., 1939 Dec. 12
  - Schroetter, Paul (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 5; 4p
  - Schropp, Simon (Box 80)
    - To Boas bill for maps & atlases, 1889 June 11
  - Schubert, C. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 27; 2p
  - Schuchard, G.C.L. (Box 80)
    - See FB open letter, Spain, Replies., 1938 Jan.
  - Schuchart, Th. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 4
  - Schuchhardt, C. (Box 80)
    - From Boas
    - Open letter, 1939 Jan. 18; 2p
      - enc. with FB To Steinen, W., 1939 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 26
  - Schücking, [UNK] L. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 11
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 28; 4p
  - Schucking, W. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1933 June 3; 2p
  - Schuh (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 19
  - Schüler (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15
  - Schüler, Arthur (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 31
  - Schüler [?], E. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1925 May 25
  - Schuler, R. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1923 April 23
  - Schuller, Rudolf R. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 29
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 21
    - From Boas, 1926 Sep. 7
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1929 May 10
    - From Boas, 1929 May 13
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 21
    - From Boas, 1931 May 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 26; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 19
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1917 May 2
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 16; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1925 May 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 12; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 14; 5p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 23; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 24; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 15; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 6; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 23; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 17
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1929 Mar. 16
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1929 Mar. 25; 4p
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1929 Apr. 21; 3p
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1929 Apr. 23; 3p
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1929 May 4; 4p
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1929 May 8; 2p
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1929 May 11; 4p
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1929 May 14; 2p
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1929 July 15; 2p
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1929 Oct. 21
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1930 Apr. 16
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1930 May 14
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1930 Nov. 3
    - Report on S. Am. languages, 1930 Dec. 6
  - Schultes, Richard E. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1937 June 20
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 29
  - Schultz, Adolph H. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1924 June 4
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 9
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 22
    - From Martin, Rud., 1922 Dec. 7; 3p
  - Schultz, H. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 7
  - Schultz, W.H.R. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 30
  - Schultz, Wolfgang (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 20; 2p
  - Schultz, Wolfram (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 10
      - Food draft drawn on; Am. Relief Admin.
  - Schultze, Ernst (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 9
  - Schultze, Richard (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1886 Apr. 27
  - Schultze-Jena, L. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1930 May 13
    - From Boas, 1930 May 27
    - From Boas, 1930 June 4
    - From Boas, 1930 June 20
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 21
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 28
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1935 Sep. 16
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6
    - To Boas, 1929 June 29
    - To Boas, 1930 May 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 28; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 11
    - To Boas, 1931 July 23; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 6
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 23; 2p
  - Schulz, C.E. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 22
  - Schulz, G.F. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 9
  - Schumacher (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1925 July 16
    - To Boas, 1925 July 2; 2p
  - Schumacher, Hermann (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 15
  - Schuman, Frederick L. (Box 80)